Guide to the Yale-China Association Bachelor Program Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale-China Association bachelor program records
1916-1986
RU 234
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of selection committee records, applications, orientation and program materials, correspondence, and oral history transcripts documenting the bachelor program of the Yale-China Association.
Yale-China Association
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See inventory for details
Scope and Contents
The records consist of selection committee records, applications, orientation and program materials, correspondence, and oral history transcripts documenting the bachelor program of the Yale-China Association
Missions -- China; Yale-China Association
- Records of the Bachelor program, 1916-1986; Accession 1993-A-085
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2022. Access to the oral history transcripts requires the permission of the Yale-China Association.
  - Yale Bachelors, 1970 - 1978 (Box 1)
  - Changsha Bachelors and Regular Appointees, 1973 - 1979 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Recruitment Materials, 1969 - 1974 (Box 1)
  - Selection Committee: Bachelors Recruiting, 1971 - 1974 (Box 1)
  - Inventory of Forms in Application for Bachelor Appointments, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Selection Committee: Bachelors Recruiting, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Selection Committee, 1975 - 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Selection Committee, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Selection, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Selections, 1984 - 1985 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Alternate Placement, 1986 January - April (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program Prior to 1979, 1975 -1979 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program, 1977 - 1979 (Box 1)
  - PRC Bachelors Programs, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Application and Applicants, 1980 - 1982 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Miscellany, 1979 - 1980 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Miscellany, 1980-1985 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Miscellany, 1985 - 1986 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Orientation, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Orientation, Killam's Point Conference Center, Brandford, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Bachelors Programs: Orientation, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: TESOL, 1980-1982 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Program: Wuhan, 1979-1982 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor's Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor's Logs, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - Bachelors and Yin C., Letters and Papers, 1916-1982 (Box 1)
  - Shatin Chronicles, Bachelor's Letters, 1976 -1977 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor: General Correspondence, 1973 - 1978 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Correspondence, 1982 - 1983 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Hong Kong, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1981-1984 (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Huazhong Normal University, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Hunan Medical College, 1980-1984 (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Huber Medical College, 1982 - 1983 (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: New Haven, 1980-1984 (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Correspondence: Wuhan University, 1980-1984 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Drueker, David, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Hutchins, Francis S., 1981 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Hutchins, Louise, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Lao Yuanxiu, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Norelius, Jessie P., 1984 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Rudin, Harry R., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Weigle, Richard D., 1985 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Transcripts: Xu, Hai-Lan, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - 1934 Chaugsha Revisited, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Yale Bachelor Pamphlet Project, 1977 - 1979 (Box 2)
  - Bachelors: Marriage Poll, 1973 October - December (Box 2)
  - Bachelor Reunion, 1984 (Box 2)